Kush Kumar Kundan 🕡 Featured

Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, C#, ASP.NET MVC, Entity Framework, LINQ, HTML, CSS, AZURE, JavaScript, JQuery, Web API



Current Designation: Senior Software Developer Total Experience: 6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Sasken Communication Technologies Ltd Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project

Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, C#, ASP. NET MVC, Entity

Framework, LINQ, HTML, CSS, Azure, JavaScript, JQuery, Web API

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Having 5.4 Years of experience in .net software design, analysis, development, testing and implementation of web and client server applications.

Using C# ASP.Net MVC, Entity framework, LINQ, WEB API, OData, Microsoft Azure

Experienced in Tiered architecture as well as Layered architecture.

Experience in java script, JQuery.

Experience in MVC Design Pattern

Ability to learn & develop using new technologies quickly.

Work Experience

Sasken Communication Technologies Ltd as Senior Software Developer Aug 2020 to Till Date

.NET Developer using ASP.NET MVC, WEB API, AZURE, Javascript, JQuery, Entity framework, Git, TFS ..etc

Capgemini as Software Developer -Dot Net

Feb 2019 to Aug 2020

Project Title: One share [2019 FEB -Till]

Used technology ASP.NET MVC, Web API, JavaScript, JQuery, Entity framework, LINQ

This product application is a web based responsive app, which is mean for incorporating with different cloud technologies such as

Microsoft azure

Amazon AWS

Google Cloud

It is having large set of API(s) Implementation from different cloud environment to communicate and manage the resource(s) such as, Creating & Scaling the cloud resource, and showing it to it graphical representation

It provides interfaces such as

creating VM (virtual machine)

shut down the virtual machine

Creating the billing report (Monthly &yearly based)

Showing the report in graphical representation

Report about Maximum & minimum consumed resource (user who held the resource).

Resources occupied by the user with their name & occupied

Date & the releasing resources date

User management

Admin management and many more features which user can handle without going to the respective clod provider site(s)

L&T Infotech as Software Engineer

Oct 2016 to Feb 2019

Project Title: Campus [2016 OCT -2019 FEB]

Client: Microsoft

Used technology SharePoint office 365, Web API, OData JQuery, JavaScript, Entity framework, LINQ

Role: Server Side coding & Client side Technology Domain: CMS (Content management system

This project is developed on office 365 & Azure; it enables to manage the content within organization

Content could be a simple document, media file through the site specific to the user role and responsibility, it is enabled

with features such as Document custom Event

Notification Web job

Both Provided hosted app & SharePoint hosted implementation as per requirement

Accessibility for visually disabled person

Appinsight Integration to monitoring the Application

Web job to trigger the event Customized List and Library

Dotcastle Technosolution Pvt. Ltd

Jul 2014 to Mar 2016

. Project Title: Asset management System Client: Whirlpool [2015 Sept to 2016 March]

Used technology Asp.Net MVC, Web API, JQuery, Bootstrap, Entity framework, LINQ

Role: Server Side coding,

Project on: Asset management System Description: Domain [Inventory system]

Asset management system is a web application which is use for tracking goods such as Asset, Item, BOM (Bill of material)

within an organization. It provides features of

Loaning
Loan Issuance
Maintenance
Repairing
Email notification

Report generation

Excel import

Project Title: Health Central Plus [web portal & smart device app]
Client: Restore Health Services Private Limited [July 2014-March2016]

Role: .NET Developer

Technical environment: MVC, Entity Frame work, LinQ, Webapi,Bootstrap, JQuery,, SQL Server 2012, Visual studio 2013 Description: Health Central's objective is to create a "Health Access" system that is transparent, easy to avail and timely. Health Central will ensure that information with respect to specialization, expertise, facilities and costs at the clinics, hospitals, labs which are on Health Central network, is shared with the prospective patient. This would enable the user to make a well-informed choice in line with the need and affordability. Health Central aims to ensure that the patient and his family focus on treatment and recovery and not get unduly concerned with when, who, where and how of the access and logistics.

Responsibilities:

Involved in server side codeing/ Bug fixing Working with JQgrid, Ck editor, validating

Education

UG: B.Sc (Maths) from RN COLLEGE in 2009

PG: MCA (Computers) from National Institute of Engineering (NIE) in 2013

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

AZ-203

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
C#		2020	5 Year(s) 9 Month(s)	
ASP.Net MVC			5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)	
Entity Framework		2020	5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)	
LINQ, HTML and CSS			5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)	
AZURE		2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
Javascript and JQuery			5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)	
Web API, OData		2020	5 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
SQL Server			5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)	
sql server management studio		2020	5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)	
Visual Studio 2010/2013/15/17/19		2020	5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)	
TFS & SVN		2020	5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time